<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kalamata Tour Guide</string>

    <string name="location">Location</string>

    <string name="city">The City</string>

    <string name="kalamata">Kalamata</string>
    <string name="old_town">Old Town</string>
    <string name="railway">Railway Park</string>
    <string name="seaside">A Walk on the Seaside</string>
    <string name="central_square">Central Square</string>

    <string name="must_see">Must See</string>

    <string name="castle">Castle of Isabeau</string>
    <string name="archaeological_museum">Archaeological Museum of Messenia</string>
    <string name="costumes_museum">Museum of Traditional Greek Costumes</string>
    <string name="ancient_messene">Ancient Messene</string>
    <string name="methoni">Castle of Methoni</string>
    <string name="towers">Towers of West Mani</string>

    <string name="must_do">Must Do</string>

    <string name="city_biking">City Biking</string>
    <string name="rafting">Rafting</string>
    <string name="diving">Scuba Diving</string>
    <string name="sea_kayaking">Sea Kayaking</string>
    <string name="hiking">Hiking</string>
    <string name="horse_riding">Horse Riding</string>

    <string name="must_eat">Must Eat</string>

    <string name="figs">Figs</string>
    <string name="olive">Olives and Olive Oil</string>
    <string name="sfela">Sfela Cheese</string>
    <string name="sausages">Sausages with Orange</string>
    <string name="lalagia">Lalagia</string>
    <string name="diples">Diples</string>
    <string name="pasteli">Pasteli</string>

    <string name="events">Events</string>


    <string name="dart_war">Dart War</string>
    <string name="dance_fest">International Dance Festival</string>
    <string name="fest_miden">Festival Miden</string>

    <string name="description_city">Between the peaks of Mt Taygetos and the gulf of Messinia, Kalamata
        dances to a different tune. Kalamata is Messinia’s capital and the second-largest city in the
        Peloponnese. /n Built on the site of ancient Pharai, Kalamata takes its modern name from a
        miracle-working icon of the Virgin Mary known as kalo mata (good eye). </string>

    <string name="description_oldtown">The Old Town, the exquisite beautiful region at the foot of the
        Castle, boasts the Metropolitan Panagia Ipapanti church (1873), the 12th century Kalograion
        Monastery with the renowned silk weaving workshop, and the Byzantine church Agioi Apostoloi
        (13th century) with the brick enclosed masonry. The area is the hotspot for the city’s youth,
        for it is the beating heart of the nightlife in Kalamata and by no means will it be still!</string>

    <string name="description_railway">Blowing the whistle on... The Railway Museum: One of Greece’s
        first theme parks, its steam locomotives, diesel engines, passenger and freight cars and
        two-storey central station building make it a treat for kids of ALL ages! \n
        All aboard for a ride into a bygone era.</string>

    <string name="description_seaside">The seaside road in front of the city’s extensive beach (4 km
        length with marvellous waters). On the seaside of Kalamata, people can swim in crystal clear
        waters and enjoy lace-like beaches, which have been granted the Blue Flag award of quality.
        Along the seaside, there are several tavernas, ouzo restaurants, cafeterias, bars, clubs,
        whereas beach aficionados can enjoy all kinds of water sports.</string>

    <string name="description_central">The spacious central Vassileos Georgiou (King George) square
        with many coffee shops, meeting places and strolling venues for residents and visitors. The
        pedestrian walkway of Aristomenous Street starts here with many stores and coffee shops to
        populate it.</string>

    <string name="description_castle">The point of reference par excellence in the city of Kalamata
        is the legendary “castle of Isabeau”. It is amphitheatrically constructed on the site of the
        Farai acropolis offering a bird’s eye view of the city. Constructed in the 13th century by
        William Villehardouin, it underwent subsequent additions and conversions by the Venetians and
        the Turks. Nowadays, it is an ideal open air venue for theatre, music and dance shows.</string>

    <string name="description_archaeological">This partially interactive, child-friendly museum focuses 
        on treasures found in four regions – Kalamata, Pylia, Messini and Trifylia. Exhibits include 
        everything from sculpture, pottery and funereal objects found in tholos (Mycenaean tombs shaped 
        like a beehive) at Nestor's Palace, to Roman mosaics, gold jewellery and votive offerings. 
        It provides wonderful context to the surrounding areas.</string>

    <string name="description_costume">Opened in 2017, this stunning museum is thanks to one individual,
        Victoria Karelia, who donated her remarkable collection of Greek costumes to a group known
        as the "Lyceum of Hellenic Women of Kalamata". Far from moth-eaten old hand-me-downs,
        the clothing showcases male and female folk dress from the 18th to 20th centuries in beautifully
        curated, dramatically lit exhibits.</string>

    <string name="description_messene">One of the most significant archaeological sites is Ancient
        Messene which is located just outside of Mavromati village, 30 km from the center of Kalamata.
        This is one of the most well-preserved ancient city in Greece, which to this day manages to
        maintain the prestige of yesteryear, leaving its visitors impressed. The city was named after
        the mythical Queen Messini, daughter of King Triopios of Argos. The city remained the cultural
        center of Messinia until 395, when the invasion of the Goths of Alaric gave the decisive
        blow to the city. </string>

    <string name="descritpion_methoni">Built in 1209 by the Venetians, the castle of Methoni lies at
        the southernmost point of the Peloponnese and is one of the greatest fortifications in the
        Mediterranean, occupying an area of about 9.3 hectares. </string>

    <string name="description_towers">Anyone that has heard of Mani brings to mind the impressive and
        imposing tower houses that have been taken out of the area\'s noble past and constructed with
        the traditional stone from Mani. West (Messinian) Mani belongs to Messinia. There you will
        observe these buildings, which are a representation and reflection of each family's power
        and status in society. </string>

    <string name="description_rafting">Rafting is an activity for all ages where everybody, given
        that they are physically and mentally healthy can participate. The activity includes a 45
        minutes preparation time, 2.5 hours river descend, 30 minutes swimming, relaxing, The descents
        are performed if the conditions (river level) are proper.</string>

    <string name="description_diving">Dive into a magical world with almost zero gravity, where you
        will encounter a breathtaking seabed that will impress you with abundant colors
        and unique inhabitants. </string>

    <string name="description_biking">Explore the town of Kalamata on a bike. Opt for this means of
        transport to wander around the beach, the town center and the town\'s historical center,
        following in the locals\' footsteps. Get a bike then and scour every corner of the Messinian
        capital. You should know that Kalamata has a developed bicycle network, so getting around
        on a bike will be safe. </string>

    <string name="description_kayaking">Sea kayaking is indeed one of our most popular trips offering
        an inch by inch exploration of the rich in imagery and diversity, lacy coastline of the
        Messinian Mani. Paddle in warm crystal-clear waters, exploring hidden coves and impressive
        rock formations. Visit sea caves and discover idyllic beaches sprouted between the fishing
        villages of the region.</string>

    <string name="description_horse">Escape from the everyday routine and spend your free time
        visiting the facilities of the Kalamata Riding Club, in the city\'s west coast. It is a
        modern riding school operated in accordance with European standards and offers basic,
        sports, free-style, therapeutic riding lesson and it also provides
        lairage for private horses.</string>

    <string name="description_hiking">The Hellenic Mountaineering Club of Kalamata has been operating
        since 1993 and organizes various hiking, mountain climbing, rock climbing and ascents on a
        weekly basis. As a member of the Hellenic Federation of Mountaineering and Climbing it has
        been approved by the General Secretariat of Sports and has taken the initiative to promote
        the ecosystem of Mt. Taygetos to that of a National Park. In this natural setting, will learn
        to love nature during your stay in Kalamata and the wider area.</string>

    <string name="description_war">The war of darts (saitopolemos), which takes us back many centuries,
        is revived every Easter Sunday evening at 20.30 at the old Slaughterhouses on the west coast
        of Kalamata.</string>

    <string name="description_dance">Established in 1995, the Kalamata International Dance Festival
        constitutes the key event of Kalamata\'s International Dance Center. Its purpose is to promote
        the art of dance through research, education, artistic activities and creativity.</string>

    <string name="description_miden">Festival Miden was the first Greek video art festival to be
        presented in open public spaces in 2005. Since then it has been gradually established as
        one of the most successful and interesting festivals in Greece and abroad and constitutes
        a significant attraction of cultural interest. The events take place in open public spaces
        in Kalamata\'s historical center in July and the main purpose of the festival is the free
        presentation, promotion and development of Greek and international
        video art and new media art.</string>

    <string name="description_figs">Try the “guru” of figs in Kalamata and taste the ancient
        athletes’ “drug”. It’s a dried fruit with a heap of vitamins and once you’ve had it,
        it’s going to become your healthy lifestyle companion for life.</string>

    <string name="description_olive">These tiny olives are the ambassadors of Messenia and they are
        considered to be the world\'s best. They are handpicked during harvest and this is why they
        preserve the top quality taste and nutritive you’re looking for in your diet.</string>

    <string name="description_sfela">If you like feta cheese, then you should try the saltier member
        of this cheese family. It’s called Sfela and its nickname is “the feta that’s on fire”.
        Sfela is a traditional product of Messenia that’s produced from sheep and goat milk,
        with no other substances or enhancers.</string>

    <string name="description_sausages">Discover an artisan form of sausage that’s made with love
        in Kalamata. It has a very interesting taste, which is based on its spicy red peppers
        that are cooled down a bit by the refreshing orange slices.</string>

    <string name="description_lalagia">The lalaggia are the main festive sweet that is prepared and
        offered during the Christmas period in Messinia. </string>

    <string name="description_diples">Diples is a popular dessert in the whole of the Peloponnese,
        but the Kalamata version has an extra twist. The talented women of the region thought of
        adding some refreshing orange zest, which makes a yummy difference.</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
